Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Ahhhhhhh!
Nice observation skills.
You really are quite the animal.
Regardless, it's already over now.
Over? What is?
You've fulfilled your purpose here.
Take your leave, Radies, before the other knights arrive.
It's little Oster, right?
Don't worry, I promise to kill you soon enough!
And make a plaything of your corpse!
Something we can both look forward to, you brat!
Spatial magic is still magic!
And I've still got my sword!
I'm gonna hack that spell to pieces!
The hell?
That hurts!
You're gonna pay for that, you little wretch!
Unfortunate.
You're whining about a little cut, after the pain you've caused!
You want pain?
I'll give you pain!
You tortured innocent people and laughed the whole time!
So what should I do?
I can't afford to lose Radies just yet.
How pitiful.
I come here after receiving word from the Master.
Only to arrive and find you fighting this?
Pitiful indeed.
So now there's five of them?
This curse I've got on me.
None of these scrapes and scratches will stop bleeding.
Looks like the tables have finally turned!
I move.
Ones in a long way.
This is the only one.
So few of our elders.
hello
Yeah, yeah!
Honestly I apologize's saloon
Mm hmm, mm hmm
It's gotten a lot quieter out there.
Is the invasion over?
It's so good.
I can't move.
Oh, my beautiful savior of sustenance.
I wonder what happened to those knights who saved me.
I hope they're okay.
Hosta!
What was that?
Small surgery.
Now I'm ready to fight again.
Watch.
I'll prove it to you.
Seriously?
Did he just strike himself with his own blades to dispel the curse?
Unbelievable!
Who would do that?
This kid's funny.
Can I pretty please dissect him later?
Be quiet and focus.
Phooey, you're no fun.
Here's the thing.
I've been fighting an uphill battle since I was born.
No matter how many guys you've got,
and no matter what you do to me,
I'll cut right through every last one of you!
You hear me?
Let's see what you've got!
Has the threat of our superior numbers driven him mad?
What's it matter anyway?
I can still dissect a crazy person.
Such a pointless flailing about.
The brat doesn't know when to give up!
Oh, I know who you are.
This must be the anti-magic boy the Master mentioned.
Your brash fearlessness may well be the greatest weapon you have,
but you must learn to remain calm.
That is, if you truly do wish to be the Wizard King.
You got it, Captain.
I can do calm.
I'm gonna calmly tear you to pieces!
Not likely.
Flame magic!
Exploding flame!
You think I'm gonna let you get away with what you did to my brother?
One of us is going down today, and it's not gonna be me!
How you doing, Asta?
You got room for one more?
Sure thing!
Feel free to jump in whenever you want to!
They fight like wounded beasts,
cornered with nothing left to lose.
They're fearless!
What are you waiting for?
Just get rid of these idiots already!
What do you think we're doing?
This wasn't our original objective.
But you've made yourselves targets!
Thanks, Noelle!
If those fools thought I'd let them kill my friends that easily,
then they were sorely mistaken!
Hey!
That's some pretty spiffy defensive magic!
Interesting.
This girl has the look of the Royal House Silver.
Well, in that case,
we should respond with something appropriate to her exalted station.
Tree creation magic!
Magic draining roots!
Master!
I got it!
What are you planning to do?
Oh, no!
His counterspell swallowed up the torrent!
Admirable battle instincts,
but it won't be enough!
Wind creation magic,
death by tornado needles!
He was too fast!
Are you okay?
Please say something!
Now,
to finish this for good.
I can't help.
Please, no!
Ooh, how fun!
I've never since magic like this before!
What?
You're back!
The rest of the magic knights!
No!
Did you think a little distance would be enough to save you?
You're back.
How from so far?
We work together to effect our return.
The cooperation doesn't come naturally to us.
If I had to give this spell a name,
I'd call it Super Compound Magic.
Merging our talents rather than vying for dominance.
What a novel idea!
Well, I guess we can't write off men entirely, huh?
Yes.
It appears they can be useful on occasion.
This cooperation business leaves a bad taste in my mouth.
We Silver Eagles have never been known for playing well with others.
And yet,
it is the duty of all magic knights to protect the kingdom.
If we must work together to do that, then so be it.
What happened here?
He's badly hurt.
Do you think you can help?
How horrible!
Who could do this to a man as strong as Captain Fugolion?
Come on!
Somebody check the others!
Are they still breathing?
Come on, Asta!
Wake up for me!
Good!
He's alive!
To have brought down fighters as strong as these three,
how powerful are they?
Our losses will be too high if we continue this fight.
Retreat!
What leaving so soon?
Mercury Magic!
Reign of Silver!
Gel Magic!
Go Sticky Salamander!
It will take a far more powerful spell than that to withstand my Silver Rain.
Think so?
Dark Magic Item!
Property Boost Absorb!
Woohoo!
That's impossible!
It's soaking up the Captain's magic like it's nothing!
But how?
What sort of magic item is that?
Asta!
And gotcha!
What do you plan to do with him?
It's a secret!
We'll leave you for now.
But remember this day, Magic Knights.
We are the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
And we will bring the Clover Kingdom to its knees!
Asta!
Gel Magic!
Go Sticky Salamander!
It will take a far more powerful spell than that to withstand my Silver Rain.
Think so?
Dark Magic Item!
Property Boost Absorb!
That's impossible!
It's soaking up the Captain's magic like it's nothing!
But how?
What sort of magic item is that?
Asta!
And gotcha!
What do you plan to do with him?
It's a secret!
We'll leave you for now.
But remember this day, Magic Knights.
We are the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
And we will bring the Clover Kingdom to its knees!
Asta!
They took Asta!
But he...
Let's follow them!
Stop, Noel.
It won't work.
Why not?
We have no means of tracking them and no way to know what awaits us if they are found.
I don't care!
Let it go.
Our priority right now is strengthening the Royal Capital's defenses.
For all we know, there could be more enemies about.
We have neither time nor magic to waste on somebody like him.
How is Fuegolion?
Will he survive?
I've done all I can with my magic, but it won't be enough.
We need to get him to the medical ward for more advanced healing spells as soon as we can!
We don't have much time!
A one-armed squad, Captain.
Is there any sight more pitiful?
This is what House Fuegolion has become?
It almost makes me ashamed to be a royal.
How could you say that?
The Captain fought bravely.
Because we are magic knights.
If we do not win, we may as well not exist.
Trying counts for nothing?
Less than nothing.
The Crimson Lion Kings are ruined now.
Enough, Solid!
We weren't here to fight, and that makes us even less than him.
Now see to the town's defenses.
This is no time for your adolescent posturing.
Right.
There's some sort of spell blocking transmission magic.
The chain of command is in chaos.
That explains why outside reinforcements never arrived.
Everyone stay sharp!
We need to secure the perimeter.
Keep your eyes open.
You bet, Char!
Call me Captain, Sol.
Okay, securing the perimeter, Captain Char.
At the right things are going,
I don't know when I'm ever going to have time for that dessert.
Quick, Klaus.
Go.
Return to HQ for backup.
Right.
Hasta.
Raides, you put your petty need for revenge ahead of the mission, and this is the result.
The Master may have taken a liking to you, but don't get cocky.
Mocking about with those creatures of yours, taking on the Captain by yourself, you're an arrogant fool.
Give it a rest already.
If you had stuck to the plan like you were supposed to, things would have been much less complicated.
I don't see what you have to complain about when it was my precious puppets that were the victims of all of this.
Let's not forget about Catherine. Things didn't turn out too well for her either.
As if I care about that old hag.
Quit squabbling.
I don't know why everyone's so upset you got what you wanted, right?
Oh, and Sally, one thing.
This little prize of yours can't come with us.
Kill him.
What?
You've got to be kidding.
I can't just throw away a prime specimen like him.
We're not talking about simple magic weakening spells.
This kid has actual anti-magic.
Where am I?
What is this stuff?
It feels sort of nice.
Only those people who have been acknowledged by the Master may go where we are headed.
We don't need more unnecessary trouble.
Kill him before the Master comes for us.
You know I'd be happy to kill him for you.
The brat would make a good addition to my playthings.
You stay out of it, Raiden.
Not good.
No fair.
Looks like I've gotten myself captured.
Goody, goody, you're awake.
A girl?
Come on, you should help me convince them.
It'll be great.
I'll study everything about you and your grimoire and do some experiments,
and then I'll dissect you.
You want to help with my research, don't you?
I'll analyze every last cell.
Nothing will go to waste, I swear.
Just think of how much we can learn.
This girl is completely nuts.
I'll be like to say.
I am in seriously deep trouble.
Crap, I can't move.
There's no getting out of here.
Are you going to make me beg, York?
Because I will.
Pretty, pretty, pretty, please.
Whatever you do, just leave me out of it.
Give him to me!
No way!
Hi there.
You've kept me waiting.
What?
Ooh!
No!
It can't be!
The Wizard King, Julius Novokrono.
How did he find us?
Why is he here?
Did you have a pleasant visit to the capital?
Kill him now!
They're gone!
How did you-
Yeah, sorry about that.
It would have been too difficult to restrain all of you.
Much easier for me this way.
You started this.
It was your choice to attack the capital.
And now you're nervous?
Don't tell me you came to kill without being prepared to die yourselves.
So strong.
But what did I expect?
He is the Wizard King.
And with my magic power drained.
Tell you what.
You're skilled enough to make this a bit of a challenge.
But I'd rather not go to the trouble.
So let's make a deal.
I'll let the first person to surrender survive.
Well, do we have any takers?
Don't be shy.
Not happening!
How is he moving like that?
He's so fast, I can't even see him!
A test then.
We'll see if it will work on this many.
Time binding magic.
Chronostasis!
What did he do?
Bodies frozen.
Can't move.
Well, would you look at that?
I got you all.
Guess I overestimated your skills.
I hope you enjoyed this moment because you're going to be stuck like that for a while.
Ow, ow, ow.
Oh, Asta, there you are.
It's nice to see you again.
We keep running into each other.
Uh, yeah.
That many powerful mages and he captured them all?
It shouldn't be possible.
But he pulled it off.
Amazing.
You want to be the Wizard King someday.
Isn't that right?
Then I suggest you carefully consider everything you've seen here.
This was only the smallest example of the sort of power you'll have to outmatch.
This is who I'm chasing.
The strongest man I've ever met.
The most powerful mage in the kingdom.
And the one I have to surpass.
Can you stand?
The Wizard King and all his power.
Right here in front of me.
Idiot!
Stop shaking!
Don't look weak!
Well, it would seem you don't need help after all.
As much as I hate to admit it, you folks have some pretty neat magic.
It surprised me.
Now then, there are quite a few questions I'd like for you to answer.
This tablet you have here with the jewels.
What is it for?
I've never seen writing like this, nor such a pattern.
What exactly were you trying to accomplish with it?
Actually, hold that thought.
You can't very well answer while caught up in my spell now, can you?
We'll have a nice chat about it later back in the Clover Kingdom.
Get ready.
Something's coming.
So great!
Where is this light coming from?
Bye, bye.
Bye.
I can't find a place to go
Break free yourself
終わらない夢を掴むため
進むべき道があるなら
Do you wanna drive? Do you wanna drive?
このままどこまででも
僕の命が終わるまで
どんな痛みも受け入れよう
We can try again
たとえ明日が見えなくても
声にならない
思いを抱いて
叫び続ける今
ご視聴ありがとうございました
You should try it over rice sometime
Totally delicious
This girl is crazy
Yum I want a bowl
That one is too
Wow
I can't believe the wizard king himself showed up
I wonder if I could get him to be the subject
For my next experiment
Black clover
Page 27
Light
I'm always looking for new specimens
Just ask for Sally
You should try it over rice
When I could get the light check
Please remain asleep
You should try it over рус stupid
Not like honey
No
But for high school
I go to glue
manos
Technic
Nome
Tu
ięcy
Totally
Not like
世
頃
sized